{
    "subject": "resource/Neil_Simon's_I_Ought_to_Be_in_Pictures",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Herbert_Ross",
    "human_readable": "The director of Neil Simon's I Ought to Be in Pictures is Herbert Ross.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7962215542793274,
            "question": "Who directed the movie I Ought to Be in Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7641364336013794,
            "question": "Are there any other works by Neil Simon besides I Ought to Be in Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7480921149253845,
            "question": "Is Herbert Ross a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6410797238349915,
            "question": "Name a famous film directed by Herbert Ross."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6370341777801514,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie directed by Herbert Ross?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5960574150085449,
            "question": "Who wrote the play I Ought to Be in Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45695772767066956,
            "question": "What year was I Ought to Be in Pictures released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4464709162712097,
            "question": "What genre is the movie I Ought to Be in Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3808901011943817,
            "question": "Has Herbert Ross won any awards for his directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3703707158565521,
            "question": "What is the main theme explored in I Ought to Be in Pictures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Neil Simon's I Ought to Be in Pictures is Herbert Ross.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7063_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Herbert Ross won any awards for his directing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7063_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie I Ought to Be in Pictures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7063_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was I Ought to Be in Pictures released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7063_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7063_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Herbert Ross directed the film \"Neil Simon\u2019s I Ought to Be in Pictures,\" supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}